https://promguide.com/privacy-policy/

Search
Prom Guide – Your Prom, Quinceañera, Pageant, Sweet 16, Homecoming Planner
Pageants
AllFiesta Teen QueenMiss Black AmericaMiss Teen USAMrs. India USAPure International PageantsUSA National Miss
Terani Couture
Watch: Terani Couture Fall 2019 Fashion Show
Pure International Pageants
Pure International Pageants – Pageant of the Year Multi – Division
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in United States privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your PII in accordance with our websites, mobile and other applications and social platforms on which it is posted (each referred to herein as a “Site”).
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our Sites?
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, age, date of birth, wireless device messaging address, screen name or username, photograph, gender, geolocation information, payment card and other payment information, event information, information about your family, your high school, date of graduation, date of event, interests, hobbies and demographic information and/or other details to help you with your experience.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you visit, register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, edit your profile, enter sweepstakes and contests, apply for scholarships, comment in chat room, bulletin board, blog or other social forum on the Site or submit a comment or question to us by using a “contact us” or similar feature on the Site.  In some instances, you may not be able to participate in certain activities or access certain content, unless you provide us with the requested personal information.
Our Site, emails, and other communications allow you to send information about our Sites and offerings to another person. In some cases, when you use these services, we will request the name or other information (i.e. email addresses) of the other person.  Their information will be treated according to this policy.  We may automatically send the other person who you indicated an invitation to read an article, view the content, or visit the site.  We store this information for purposes of sending the email and tracking the success of our sharing features.  Your “friend” (i.e., the third party whose information you submit using such feature) may contact us at promguide@promguide.com to request that we remove this information from our database and in some cases, they may be able to opt out of receiving future promotional emails from us.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the site, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
• To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
• To improve our site in order to better serve you.
• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
• To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.
• To develop new features and offerings on the site.
• To send you marketing and other communications, including information about products, services, and events, of ours and of others. You may opt of receiving such notices from us by following the instructions.
• To protect our rights and property.
• To customize the site to your interests and history with us.
• To tailor ads displayed to you on our site and elsewhere to your interests and history with us.
• To utilize for other purposes described at the time you choose to provide your personal information to us.
To perform the above functions, we may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both personal and site usage information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources (including third parties) such as demographics information and updated contact information. We or our service providers may also use your information to assess the level of interest in, and use emails and our other messaging campaigns both on an individual basis and in the aggregate.
How do we protect visitor information?
Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.
We use regular Malware Scanning.
Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.
All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.
Do we use ‘cookies’?
We do use cookies for tracking purposes.  In addition to the general purposes listed above, cookies allow us to recognize you as the same user who was at our Site in the past, and relate your use of the Site to other information about you, such as other information and personal information.  Cookies may also be used to enhance your experience on the Site (i.e. storing your username), gain general usage information and aggregated statistical information.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If you disable cookies, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services may not function properly.
However, you can still place orders.  By using our Site, you agree to these tracking technologies.
Third Party Disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include site hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our sites, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.  However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our sites. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Google
Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
We have or will implement the following:
• Remarketing with Google AdSense
• Google Display Network Impression Reporting
• Demographics and Interests Reporting
• DoubleClick Platform Integration
We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
Opting out:
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.
You may have the right to opt in to or opt out of certain of our uses and disclosures of your Personal Information.  For example, when you are asked for Personal Information on this Site, you may have the opportunity to elect to, or not to, receive promotional messages from us by email or by text.  You may unsubscribe from our promotional emails by editing your preferences in your account profile on the Site, or by clicking within the email you receive.  To opt out of our text messages, please follow the instructions provided in connection with the particular text message.  Please understand that it may take us some time to process any opt out request and that even if you opt out of receiving promotional correspondence, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us.  You may also tell us that you do share your personal information with third parties for their marketing purposes, by editing your preferences in you Site member profile or by emailing promguide@promguide.com (please include your name, mailing address, and email address).  To stop receiving promotional messages from third parties, please contact them directly.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. – See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:
-Users can visit our site anonymously.
-Link to your privacy policy on our home page.
-Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page
-Users are able to change their personal information by logging in to their account
-We respond to requests from California customers asking about businesses’ practices related to disclosing personal information to third parties for the third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes and if the customer has an option to opt-out of such information-sharing. As discussed above, if you wish to opt-out of our sharing of your information with third parties for third parties’ direct marketing purposes, edit your preferences in your account profile at https://promguide.com/members/username/settings/profile or email us at promguide@promguide.com (please include your name, mailing address, and email address).
How does our site handle do not track signals?
We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?
We do allow third party behavioral tracking.
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under 13.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
We will notify the users via email:
• Within 7 business days
We will notify the users via in site notification
• Within 7 business days
We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
• Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders
• We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.
• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred
To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:
• NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses
• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way
• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters
• Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly
• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
America’s Prom Guide, LLC | 400 Peachtree Street NW | Suite 4-1044 | Atlanta, GA 30308
Last Edited on 2015-07-10
ABOUT USProm Guide offers a first look at the season's prom, quinceañera, homecoming, sweet 16 and all teen coming-of-age event fashion and trends including insightful reviews, full collection slideshows, backstage beauty, and street style.Contact us: promguide@promguide.comFOLLOW US
Privacy Policy
© 1991 - 2019 Prom Guide
